<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 6: The Ground Game</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-10-13-blog-post-6-turnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-10-13-blog-post-6-turnout/</guid>
      <description> cvap &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;/Users/claireduncan/Downloads/polls_cvap_vp_df.csv&amp;quot;) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 5: The Air Game</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-10-08-blog-post-5-the-air-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-10-08-blog-post-5-the-air-game/</guid>
      <description>This week, we turned from studying the fundamentals of an election to the effects of campaigns themselves, starting with advertising. Are campaign commercials able to persuade voters to vote differently or to turn out in the first place? Research has found that ads have a very short effect, making them not very durable. Their effects decay just after a few days, meaning that even if voters say in the moment after watching an ad that they’ll vote for a particular candidate, a few days later they will have reverted back to their original decision (Hill, Lo, Vavreck, Zaller (2013)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 4: Incumbency</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-29-blog-post-4-incumbency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-29-blog-post-4-incumbency/</guid>
      <description>This week in Election Analytics, we covered incumbency as it creates advantages and disadvantages in election cycles. While incumbent politicians tend to be reelected, incumbent parties tend to do worse, especially in midterm years as the President’s party tends to lose the House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 3: Polling</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-22-blog-post-3-polling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-22-blog-post-3-polling/</guid>
      <description>This week in Election Analytics, we covered polling as a predictor of election results. Polling is central to understanding what the electorate wants and how they believe the government is working to achieve those goals and needs. Polling also generally allows for knowing the average opinion of the population as it can uncover a true estimate through canceling out the errors and outliers that occur within a polling sample.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 2: Economic Forces</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-blog-post-2-economic-forces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-blog-post-2-economic-forces/</guid>
      <description>In week two of Election Analytics, we focused on economic forces and the effect of various measures of economic well-being at the ballot box. Do voters punish candidates when the economy is doing poorly? Do they focus on only the short-term effects or the long-term changes over time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 1: Introduction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-10-blog-post-1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-10-blog-post-1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Claire Duncan and I’m a junior studying government and psychology at Harvard. From now until November 8, Election Day, I will be updating this blog every week with a prediction model for the upcoming 2022 US midterm elections. This week, the focus is on setting up the blog and creating visualizations of Democratic/Republican vote share and seat share during previous election years - in particular, the 2020 House of Representatives general election.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
